

Personal details



Nadya Baranava



Minsk, Belarus



linkedin.com/in/nadzeyabaranava-265b45267



github.com/Nadyushka



t.me/Nadyushka_Baranova



12nadya11@gmail.com

Skills

Vue / Nuxt / Pinia / Vuex

React / Redux / Redux Toolkit

Axios / Rest API / Postman

JavaScript / TypeScript

Unit tests / Storybook

Material UI / Mantine / Vuetify

Formik / Vee-Validate

HTML5 / CSS3 / SCSS

GIT

Swagger

Languages

English - B2

German -B1

Russian - Native

Nadya Baranava

Frontend developer

About me

I am a Front-End developer with an experience in creating SPA using Vue/Nuxt and React/Redux/TypeScript. Now I am expanding my skills in frontend development with new technologies. I spend my leisure time reading educational books and improving English and German. Open for your offers.

Experiences

Frontend developer

May 2023 - Present

BSL

Applications development using Vue 2 (Vuex) and Vue 3 (Pinia). Adding TS to exicting projects to improve development quality. Bugs fixes and adding features. Projects analysis, research and suggestions for improving users expirience and bests ideas implemention.

VUE, NUXT, VUEX, PINIA, VUETIFY, VUEXY, VEE-VALIDATE, GIT

English cards - Part-time

Mar 2023 - May 2023

Start-up project

A team SPA development.

REACT, REDUX, TYPESCRIPT, REDUX-THUNK, REACT-ROUTER-DOM, FORMIK, MUI, REST API, AXIOS, GIT, POSTMAN, SWAGGER

Todolist

Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

Educational project

Todolist was developed with the best React practices.

REACT, REDUX, TYPESCRIPT, FORMIK, MUI, REST API, AXIOS

SOCIAL NETWORKSelf-education project

Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

SOCIAL NETWORK app was developed with class and functional components, routing, login/logout flow, pagination, form validation, redirections.

REACT, REDUX, TYPESCRIPT, AXIOS

Education

Frontend developer course

Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

it-incubator

Frontend developer course

Jun 2022 - Oct 2022

The Rolling Scope school

Innovation management

Sep 2016 - Jun 2018

BNTU

Mater's degree